name	eligibility
Reliance Foundation UG Scholarship	<strong>You must fulfil the following eligibility criteria in order to apply:</strong><ul style="margin-top:10px;"><li>Be a resident Indian citizen</li><li>Passed Standard 12th with minimum 60%</li><li>Currently enrolled in the 1st year (academic year 2025-26) in a regular full-time degree course in any stream</li><li>Students having House Hold income < Rs. 15 Lakhs (preference given to < Rs. 2.5 Lakhs)</li><li>Aptitude Test is mandatory</li></ul><p style="margin-top:15px; margin-bottom:10px;"><strong>Following students are not eligible:</strong></p><ul><li>Students who are in the 2nd year or higher (have started their courses from academic year 2024-25 or before)</li><li>Students pursuing their degree through online, hybrid, remote, distance or any other non-regular modes</li><li>Students who have passed diploma after std. 10th</li><li>Students pursuing 2 year & 6 year undergraduate degree courses</li><li>Students who do not answer the mandatory aptitude test or are found cheating during the test</li></ul>
Reliance Foundation UG Scholarship	<strong>You must fulfil the following eligibility criteria in order to apply:</strong><ul style="margin-top:10px;"><li>Be a resident Indian citizen</li><li>Passed Standard 12th with minimum 60%</li><li>Currently enrolled in the 1st year (academic year 2025-26) in a regular full-time degree course in any stream</li><li>Students having House Hold income < Rs. 15 Lakhs (preference given to < Rs. 2.5 Lakhs)</li><li>Aptitude Test is mandatory</li></ul><p style="margin-top:15px; margin-bottom:10px;"><strong>Following students are not eligible:</strong></p><ul><li>Students who are in the 2nd year or higher (have started their courses from academic year 2024-25 or before)</li><li>Students pursuing their degree through online, hybrid, remote, distance or any other non-regular modes</li><li>Students who have passed diploma after std. 10th</li><li>Students pursuing 2 year & 6 year undergraduate degree courses</li><li>Students who do not answer the mandatory aptitude test or are found cheating during the test</li></ul>
Reliance Foundation UG Scholarship	<strong>You must fulfil the following eligibility criteria in order to apply:</strong><ul style="margin-top:10px;"><li>Be a resident Indian citizen</li><li>Passed Standard 12th with minimum 60%</li><li>Currently enrolled in the 1st year (academic year 2025-26) in a regular full-time degree course in any stream</li><li>Students having House Hold income < Rs. 15 Lakhs (preference given to < Rs. 2.5 Lakhs)</li><li>Aptitude Test is mandatory</li></ul><p style="margin-top:15px; margin-bottom:10px;"><strong>Following students are not eligible:</strong></p><ul><li>Students who are in the 2nd year or higher (have started their courses from academic year 2024-25 or before)</li><li>Students pursuing their degree through online, hybrid, remote, distance or any other non-regular modes</li><li>Students who have passed diploma after std. 10th</li><li>Students pursuing 2 year & 6 year undergraduate degree courses</li><li>Students who do not answer the mandatory aptitude test or are found cheating during the test</li></ul>
